Ahmed Naseem Amin

Frontend Developer

independent front-end developer with 4 years of experience in blending the art of design with the skill of programming to deliver an immersive and engaging user experience through efficient designing and building responsive websites with modern animation. Proficient with CSS and JS Frameworks.

Work Experience

Negat Company - Onsite

Egypt - Giza

1/2021 - 9/2021

- Responsible for architecting and defining the Front-end framework to solve complex designs and interactions that reflect the creative and art direction.
- Collaborated with the UX/UI design teams to improve the website, Dashboard, and convert it to real world.
- Daily maintenance of code, debugging issues and solving problems.

Finboa Company - Remotly

USA - Texas

9/2021 - 1/2022

- Integrate with back-end APIs.
- Designed and implement web applications.
- Design and develop features for an industry-leading Workload Automation product using modern front-end technologies.
- Collaborate with designers and back-end developers to implement and improve features.
- Creates optimized solutions across multiple devices and screens, including desktops, tablets, smartphones.
- Developed website redesign and improved conversions, using JAVASCRIPT and HTML5.

Tonsetech Company - Remotly

Bahrain - Manama

10/2022- Present

- Implement UI/UX designs: Transform design mockups into functional web pages using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Ensure cross-browser compatibility: Test and optimize websites to work seamlessly across different browsers.
- Create responsive designs: Develop layouts that adapt to various screen sizes and devices.
- Collaborate with team members: Work closely with UI/UX designers, backend developers

Education

- Nahia Secondary School
 - 2016 2022
- Faculty of Education

2022 - Present

Skills

- HTML5
- CSS3
- VueJS
- Javascript
- Bootstrap
- Sass
- Gulp
- Pug JS
- JQuery
- Dart
- Flutter

Contact Info



+20 1159614802

maseemamin@gmail.com

https://portfolionaseem.vercel.app/



https://github.com/anaseem80



https://www.linkedin.com/in/ anaseem60/